Frozen in Love is a romance, tv movie film directed by Scott Smith.
When struggling bookstore owner Mary and the bad boy of professional hockey, Adam, are teamed together to help facilitate an image
makeover for the other, they soon realize that opposites attract and they find themselves unexpectedly frozen in love.
Mary Campbell, played by Rachael Leigh Cook.
Adam Clayborn, played by Niall Matter.
Janet Dunleavy, played by Sandy Sidhu.
Tyler Campbell, played by Madison Smith.
Erica Parker, played by Tammy Gillis.
Kate Campbell, played by Susan Hogan.
Frozen in Love is a 2018 American-Canadian made for television romantic drama film
directed by Scott Smith and starring Rachael Leigh Cook and Niall Matter.
It was developed from an original idea by Cook.
The film was produced by the Hallmark Channel and premiered on their network in the
United States on January 13, 2018, as part of their 'Winterfest' season.
The film explores themes of winter, ice hockey, book store.
The tone is emotional.